Brock 你在干什么?
Brock? What are you doing?
为手术做准备
Getting ready for surgery.
不然干什么?
What's it look like?
躺在手术台上的是我姐姐
You're operating on my sister.
也是我未婚妻
And my fiancee.
你喝多了
You're drunk.
会害她送命的
You could kill her.
只有这样我的手才能不抖
It's the only way to stop/my hands from shaking.
我需要酒...为了Anna
I need to drink... for anna.
那我们的孩子呢?
What about...our baby?
我们的...孩子?
Our...baby?
Brock? 天啊!
Brock? Oh,my god!
Brock? 你还好吗?
Brock? Are you okay?
Brock 说话啊!
Brock,speak to me!
天啊!
Oh,my god!
他好像真的出事了
Um,I--I think he's/really hurt.
停!
Cut!
把我吓坏了
Oh...that was scary.
有那么一会我真以为你—
I thought for a second you were really—
你是世上唯一信以为真的人
you're gonna be the only/one in the world who did.
真可笑
This is ridiculous.
演得不错啊 Evan
That was great,evan.
不 糟透了
No,it wasn'T. It was crap.
影迷一定会喜欢的
The fans are gonna love it.
影迷是废物 我也是废物
The fans are crap. I'm crap.
整个该死的演出都糟透了!
This whole damn show is crap!
抱歉 不是你的错
Sorry,not your fault.
你往哪开?
Um...where are you going?
我住在西边啊
My apartment's on the west side.
你得往另一边开
Excuse me,you need to go the other way.
你听到了吗?
Hey,did you hear what I said?
搞什么鬼?
What the hell's going on here?
你想要什么?
What do you want?
亲笔签名照就不错
An autographed picture would be nice.
噢...还想顺便救你一命
Oh... and I'm also gonna save your life.
你可能要考虑重新设斑马线
You might want to think about/repositioning the crosswalk.
技术上说现在不算违规
It's technically not a violation,
但斑马线越靠近入口就利用率就越高
but the closer they are to the entrance,/the more likely they are to be used.
有道理
Makes sense.
我以为你下个月才来
I actually wasn't expecting/you till next month.
这就是计划检查的问题所在
Yeah,that's the problem/with planned visits.
管理层会为此事先准备
Administrators plan for them.
谈到最新的新泽西医院评估要求
So the most recent new jersey/hospital accreditation requirements.
是的 我熟悉—
Yeah,I'm familiar with—
这是谁?
Who is that?
我不认识
I have no idea.
我们可以开始检查了吗?
Shall we get started?
让我走
Just let me go.
我不会告你的
I won't press charges.
会把整件事都忘掉
Forget the whole thing.
可能真会忘掉
That's probably true.
得看你的脑瘤恶化到什么程度了
Seeing as how you have a brain tumor.
原来你就是那个疯医生/不断打电话骚扰我的公关
You're that nut job doctor that/keeps calling my publicist.
事实上我是诊断部门的疯头头
Actually,I'm the nut job/head of diagnostic medicine.
我每天坚持跑步
I run every day.
也没头痛 我好的很
I don't get headaches. I'm fine.
- 所以你要是不介意--/- 我很介意
- So if you don't mind--/- actually,I do mind.
我才不在意你的死活/但要是Brock Sterling死了
I don't care if you die,but/if brock sterling dies,
Anna就永远都不知道/他就是Marie孩子他爸了
anna never finds out he's/the father of marie's baby.
来人啊!
Help!
这里需要轮椅!
We're gonna need a wheelchair!
这里
Here.
最近一个月你念台词的速度/从平均2.1秒降慢到2.9秒了
Look,in the last month,your average line/reading has slowed from 2.1 seconds to 2.9.
更常停顿了
You're pausing more.
并且都在相同的间隔
Always at the same intervals.
每7到9个词停一下
Every seven to nine words.
说明你看提词机的一侧有困难
Which means you're having trouble/reading one side of the teleprompter.
证明你的周围视力有问题
Which means it's a/peripheral vision problem.
说明你的枕叶有肿瘤
Which means a tumor/in your occipital lobe.
只要做一个测试
Just one test.
要是没事的话 我马上送你回家
If there's nothing wrong,I'll/take you right back home.
给我出租车费就好
Make it cab fare.
我才不要你靠近我家
I don't want you anywhere near my house.
停到我的停车位上
Uh,just put it in my spot.
评估委员会是来保护我们及病人的
The accreditation board is here/to protect us and our patients.
所以跟调查员打交道时
So in dealing with/the on-site inspector,
请表现好点 不要被看出是装出来的
please behave as if it wasn't/also an enormous pain in the ass.
谢谢合作
Thank you.
Chase Foreman Cameron 请过来一下
Chase,foreman,cameron,up here,please.
为什么House开豪华轿车来?
Why is house driving a limo?
不知道
Don't know.
不必知道
Don't have to know.
不想知道?
Don't...care?
不对! 检查结束前你们得看着House
Wrong! Until this inspection is/over,you're back on house watch.
你负责当前的病例 你负责以前的病例
Current case,past cases.
他现在没有病例
He doesn't have a current case.
我还得负责整个部门
I have a whole department.
要是我们不照做你会解雇我们吗?
Are you gonna fire us if we don't?
我只是想你们帮帮忙而已
I was just asking for your help.
我上次查急诊室的档案时
The last time I checked the E.R.,
发现你写的病历是全院做得最好的
You had the best-kept/charts in the building.
上次我查四楼看门人的储藏室时/发现了该House写的病历
The last time I checked the fourth floor/janitor's closet,I found house's charts.
自从你走了他没做过任何档案
He hasn't filed anything since you left.
也许House不在乎医院的评估是否降格
Now,house may not care whether this/hospital's accreditation gets downgraded.
给我发工资的人却很在乎
The people who sign my paychecks do.
我再重复一次 你负责当前 你负责过去的
So I repeat,current,past.
他现在没有病例啊
He doesn't have a current case.
他跟你说过豪华轿车的事没?
Did he tell you about the limo?
见到光就按这个按钮就行了?
So I just press this button/every time I see a light?
能让我知道你的盲区在哪
It tells me where your blind spots are.
那么...那对双胞胎
So...the twins.
都是你的?
They're gonna turn out/to be yours,aren't they?
我说过不能跟你谈这些的
I told you I can't/talk about that stuff.
但是你想快点结束这个吧?
But you want to be done with this,right?
一个是我的 一个是Julio的
One's mine,one's julio's.
我早知道!
I knew it!
Julio在她患阑尾炎之前把她肚子搞大了/-- 你后来才上了她
Julio knocked her up before her/appendix burst-- you got her after.
你怎么会看这些东西?
How can you watch that stuff?
因为是部很棒的剧
'Cause it's awesome.
剧情很荒谬
It's preposterous.
我演了这么久/没有一刻是真实世界中存在的
Not one real moment since/I've been on the show.
和表达真实世界的剧集相反 例如...
As opposed to shows that represent/the world exactly the way it is,like...
我举不出例子
I can't think of any.
发生了什么事?
What's going on?
医院正被检查 Cuddy派你来看着我/这就是所发生的事
The hospital is being inspected,and/cuddy dispatched you to keep an eye on me.
我刚刚停了一部豪华轿车在救护车道上
I just parked a town/car in an ambulance bay.
cuddy没有破口大骂 却装作不认识我
And instead of  ripping me one,cuddy/acted like she didn't know me.
要不是有检查就是她患动脉瘤了
It's either an/inspection or an aneurysm.
测试显示出什么?
What's the test say?
像我怀疑的一样
As I suspected.
你视野的右上方有相当大的缺失
You have significant losses in the upper/right quadrant of your visual field.
真的?
Are you serious?
开玩笑的
No,it's a joke.
两朋友走进一酒吧/其中一个视野的右上方有缺失
Two guys go into a bar,and one has significant losses/in the upper right quadrant of his visual field.
另一个就说"那你得做个磁共振/确认一下肿瘤的形状和位置了"
And the other one says,"you're gonna need an mri/to confirm the type and location of the tumor."
读数显示他的视力正常
That readout says his vision's fine.
不正常
no,it doesn't.
正常
Yes,it does.
你骗了我?
You lied to me?
我绑架了你
I kidnapped you.
我要是骗了你还有什么好惊讶的?
You're surprised that I lied to you?
这只说明你的症状是间歇的
It just means that the/symptoms are intermittent.
你要是再接近我 我就报警了
Yocome near me again,I'm/calling the police.
你绑架了他?
You kidnapped him?
知道我还能让你惊讶真好
It's sweet that I haven't lost/the ability to surprise you.
你在学我吗?
Are you mocking me?
我的背 疼死了
My back. My back is killing me.
才不在乎 我很忙
Don't care. Busy.
Amber的可恶床垫
Amber's damn mattress.
那太糟了
Well,that sucks.
别买新的啊
Don't buy a new one.
是不是在讽刺我?
Are you being sarcastic?
因为我们正要买
Because we are buying one.
她做任何事/都非得搞得双方都得不到好处
She's incapable of doing anything that matters/without turning it into a zero-sum game.
我们是在为我们双方买床垫
We're buying a mattress for us.
我现在走得比你快了
Wow,I'm faster than you right now.
一切以她和哪个倒霉的售货员为主
It's all about her and whatever/hapless salesman wanders into her sights.
她会偷讹拐骗 牺牲你的品味/去达到她的目的
She's gonna lie,steal,and trade your/testes to get whatever she wants.
等等 不能让他按(911)第二个1
Hold on,I've just gotta do something/before he dials the second "1."
你最终会卑躬屈膝地提着她的包
You're going to end/up humiliated,holding her purse,
回家睡在你讨厌的新床垫上
and going home to sleep on/a new mattress you hate.
你在搞什么鬼?
What the hell are you doing?
他需要做核磁共振
He needs an mri.
给我照皮层下一毫米厚的片
give me one-millimeter/slices from the cortex down.
MRI是无痛检查/为什么你要给病人注射镇静剂?
Any particular reason you decided to sedate a/patient for a procedure that's completely painless?
这人在手术过程中有过激行为史
The guy has a history of violent/outbursts during surgical procedures.
那是在电视上
Yeah,on tv.
他是Evan Greer.
It's evan greer.
他是House爱看的剧里面的头号种马
He's the main stud on house's soap.
额叶皮质没事 没肿瘤
Frontal cortex looks clean. No tumors.
放大一点看枕叶
Increase the magnification on/the occipital lobe.
你看那部剧是因为你喜欢还是因为我?
You watch because you/like or because I like?
我当时失业了 而且我--
I was/unemployed,and I--
打住! 不好意思
bzzzt! Sorry.
那不是个回答 是个道歉
That's not an answer. That's an apology.
如果我们曾脱离了黑暗 我们应为此骄傲--
If we are ever to come out of the/darkness,we have to be proud--
枕叶 额叶 顶叶都没事
occipital,frontal,temporal/lobes are clean.
视神经也一样
So is the optic nerve.
肯定不是肿瘤
Definitely no tumors.
他没事?
He's fine?
而且还苏醒了
And...awake.
我们该怎么跟他说?
Uh,what should we tell him?
看能不能说服他别告我
See if you can talk him out of suing me.
他绑架了我!
He kidnapped me!
给我下药了!
He drugged me!
也许你可以从后门走
Perhaps you should go out the back way.
我才不按你们说的去做
I'm not going anywhere you/people tell me to go.
他只是你的 嗯 影迷
It's just someone of your/fame--I--I figured fans--
你们想把我藏起来
you're trying to hide me.
你不想我把事情闹大
You don't want me making a scene.
医院今天有人来检查
The hospital's being inspected today.
你们还指望我帮忙?
And you want me to do you a favor?
不是我们 是我们的院长
not us. Our dean of medicine.
House很讨厌她
And house hates her.
你要是投诉的话 就帮House大忙了
You'd be doing house/a favor by complaining.
这家医院的职员都是疯子和罪犯!
This hospital is staffed with/lunatics and crimals!
Cuddy医生在哪?
Excuse me,where's dr. Cuddy?
我脚出问题了
it's my foot.
他对我做了什么?
What did he do to me?
House做了什么?
What did house do?
没什么--我一直跟他在一起
Nothing--I was with/him the whole time.
我脚麻了
It's numb.
我感觉不到脚了
I can't feel it.
我不能走了
I can't walk.
脚部无知觉可以有很多诊断
Foot numbness has a huge differential.
加上周围视觉问题 范围就大大缩小了
It gets a lot narrower when you/add in peripheral vision problems.
如果没有证据他有视觉问题的话/那范围又扩大了
Which gets a lot wider when there's/no proof he ever had a vision problem.
这么说 最初的症状House搞错了
so house was wrong/about the first symptom,
几小时后 这家伙恰巧又冒出/第二个毫不相关的症状了?
but the guy just happened to develop a/second unrelated symptom a few hours later?
他先把人家给绑架了/又硬给人家打了镇静剂
he already kidnapped and/sedated the guy against his will.
他要是给那人下药让他腿使不上劲/走不了路 一点都不奇怪
Makes sense he'd also do something to/numb his foot so he couldn't leave.
这讲不通
But it doesn't make/sense to include a symptom
若是这个医生急着想弄清楚/又怎么会再整个症状出来
that he caused in a differential he's/so desperate to solve.
除非这并不是他有意而为之的
Unless he didn't mean to cause it.
亲爱的 好好整文档
Stick to the filing,sweetheart.
让大夫做大夫的事
Let the doctors do the doctoring.
要么是中毒 要么是维生素不足
Either toxins or vitamin deficiency.
估计你给他下镇静剂时/没扶住他放到地上
I'm guessing when you drugged him you/didn't catch him and ease him to the floor.
他可能在倒地时 压到脚踝的神经了
He ould've pinched a nerve in/his ankle when he fell.
你要做个肌电图检查/看看有没有运动神经受到压迫
You need to run an emg test/for motor nerve entrapment
不然调查员让你吃不了兜着走
or the inspector will own your ass.
Kutner 出去
Kutner,leave the room.
30分钟后回来告诉她检查结果为阴性
Wait 30 minutes. And come back/and tell her the test was negative.
我要是用这段时间/真去做那个检查可以么?
Is it okay if I use that/time to do the test?
出去吧你
Get out of here.
其他人可以帮我处理下这些
And the rest of them can/help me with all this stuff.
他们没空
They're busy.
说起来真叫人恼火
Which is really annoying because/I wanted to be able to say that
我说他们会很忙 就是想跟你捣乱
they're busy for no other/reason than to screw with you.
做研究
Research.
这么说那个疯子没说错
So the nutjob was right.
他常常是对的
Usually is.
他说我就快死了
He said I was dying.
他也有很多事说错了
He's wrong a lot too.
所以我们要做检查
That's why we do these tests.
身为热播连续剧的男主角/那感觉肯定很棒吧
I bet it's pretty cool,you/know,being the star of a hit tv show.
只是个日间肥皂剧
It's a daytime soap.
我也就比剧院餐厅的演员强点
It pretty much puts me one/step above dinner theater.
好啦 你每天都上电视
Come on. You're on tv every day.
管那些影评人说什么呢
And who cares what the critics think?
女人都爱看肥皂剧
Women love soaps.
你们的工作令你们自豪...
You get to take pride in your job...
晚上回家时感觉会很好
feel good when you go home at night.
你娱乐大众
You're entertaining people.
我不在乎
I don't care.
很奇怪你选了演员这行
Well,you've made a strange career choice.
我只是在迎合大众
Look,I'm pandering.
我希望我可以去激励别人
I want to be a part of/something that inspires people.
那就别演了
So quit.
找可以激励人的事去做
Find something inspiring and do it.
可没那么容易
It's not that easy.
为什么?
Why not?
就是不容易
Just isn't.
大夫 我的心
It's my heart,doctor.
在狂跳
It's racing.
我向你保证 你的心没事
I'm sure it's nothing.
你很健康 Marie
You're a healthy woman,marie.
不该给我检查一下么?
shouldn't you examine me?
干嘛不让Rico来检查?
why don't you have rico do it?
别跟我说 你没注意到他念台词停顿
You can't tell me you/didn't notice that pause.
抱歉
Sorry.
她不会醒的
she's never waking up.
在超高清电视上看/效果还真不同凡响呢
This is a whole new/experience in super hi-def.
我都不知道原来Marie穿内衣了
I had no idea marie wore an underwire.
听上去是有点不自然
Does sound a little forced.
他可能舌头有点不灵活/是粘液水肿的症状
Could be stiffening in his tongue/which is a symptom of myxedema.
不是舌头的问题 是对话的缘故
That's not the tongue,it's the dialogue.
我觉得我跟那护士约会过
I think I dated that nurse though.
没有
No.
他拿听诊器的方式有问题吧?
What about the way he's/holding that stethoscope?
拇指和食指间的角度很奇怪
His thumb and forefinger/are meeting at an odd angle.
可能是有毒物质导致的脱髓鞘病变
Could be demyelination from/toxic exposure.
往回倒
Back it up.
搞什么 AV俱乐部?
What's this,the av club?
在诊断病情
it's diagnostic.
一切尽在掌握
Everything's under control.
是啊
Yeah.
到目前为止 做得棒极了
Excellent job so far.
House 出来下
House,outside.
继续看
Keep watching.
你们绝对猜不出Rico在盒子里藏了什么
You'll never guess what/rico's got in that box.
Rico都不知道我还活着
rico doesn't even know I'm alive.
你对他本人或他扮演的角色/已经偏执痴迷了
You have an obsession with an/actor or the character he plays.
我感觉得到
I feel for you.
你要走出来
You need to work it out.
我需要你合作点 别威胁到医院评估/和我的乌纱帽
But I need you to do it when the/hospital's accreditation and my job are not on the line.
你希望热播的日间连续剧的主角/死在你医院里?
You want the star of the hottest daytime/drama on tv to die in your hospital?
不 我希望你循规蹈矩地把他治好
No,I want you to cure him without/committing any more felonies.
你要是让我那么束手束脚/我可干不好活儿
I can't do my job if you're/gonna tie my hands like that.
一年里51周/我纵容你像野猴子在香蕉园里撒欢
51 weeks out of the year,I let you run/around like a monkey in a banana factory.
我只是拜托你安生个几天
All I'm asking is that you/tone it down for a few days.
我要那台电视
I want that tv.
我们不是在讨价还价
We're not bargaining.
你对我有所求
You want something.
你要么讨价还价 要么低声下气
Either you're bargaining or/you're begging.
我保住工作对你有好处
Me keeping my job is good for you.
没错 但对你更有好处
Yes,but it's better for you.
我只是想皆大欢喜
I just want us to be equally happy.
肌电图测试神经压迫结果为阴性
Emg was negative for nerve entrapment.
说明他的脚失去知觉是症状
Means the foot's a real symptom.
可能是维生素不足
Could be vitamin deficiency.
或者是中毒
Or a toxin.
或者是动脉硬化
Or atherosclerosis.
或者是中毒
Or a toxin.
为什么偏向中毒?
Why is toxin a better idea?
说不准
Might not be.
检查过他的摄影场和更衣室里.../医学相关的东西后
We'll know after I'm finished searching/his set and dressing room for...
我们会清楚的
medically relevant stuff.
得走了
Gotta go.
需要做出决定
Need a decision.
你不会不计后果胡来
You're not gonna cut your own throat.
听上去像我
Yeah,that sounds like me.
检查重金属 有机物和生物毒素/检查他家
Test for heavy metals,organics,biotoxins,and/search the home.
我喜欢这枕头
I like the pillow top.
我喜欢这张
I like this one.
好眼力 这张是上品
great taste. That/model's top of the line.
多少钱?
How much is it?
$1,999 这价钱很公道
$1,999. It's a great price.
那 那张...
What about--
对我们来说太贵了
that's too rich for us.
你觉得...
I don't know,you think...
老公 我们买不起
honey,we can't afford that.
我们就要添个宝宝了
Not with a baby on the way.
恭喜了 初次为人父母?
Congratulations. Your first?
是的
Yes.
给你们优惠100块如何?
How about I knock 100 bucks off?
也许还能免费送货上门
Maybe throw in free delivery.
我们现在真的手头很紧
Money's really tight right now.
我只是个律师助理 我丈夫又刚失业
I'm a law clerk and my/husband just got laid off.
他今天要去面试
He has an interview today.
祝他好运
Wish him luck.
好运
Good luck.
祈祷我能有好运吧
Fingers crossed.
我们最多只出得起$1,500
We might be able to afford $1,500.
那我得去问下经理
Well,I-- I'd have to/check with my manager.
谢谢 真是感激不尽
Thanks. I appreciate it.
拿一下好吗?
Hold this,would you?
工作 十万火急
911 from work.
我走了
Better go.
那我是买了这硬床垫 还是去面试呢?
So am I getting the hard mattress,or/do I have to go to my job interview?
你随便买哪床都好
Whatever mattress you want.
我没意见的
I'm fine either way.
你...说真的?
You--really?
真的
Really.
只要你让我和你一起用它
Just as long as I get to/help you break it in.
快把你的男子气概收拾好冷冻起来
Pack your manhood on ice.
也许医院能让断肢再续
Maybe the hospital can reattach it.
你大错特错了
You were so wrong.
她让我做选择
She's letting me choose.
"你选"并不意味着"你做决定"
"You choose" does not mean "you choose."
是么? 听上去像是你做了选择
Really? Sounded like you choose.
我认为她想表明/House这次可是大错特错了
I suppose it's possible she/meant house is so,so wrong.
那是个套
It's a trap.
意思是 如果你爱我/你就买我想要的那个
It means if you love/me,you'll buy the one I want.
Amber不是消极攻击
Amber doesn't do passive-aggressive.
侵略型的人不喜欢约束自己
People who do aggressive/don't like to limit themselves.
电暖器泄漏会引发/视觉问题和机体麻痹吗?
Could a leaky space heater cause/vision problems and numbness?
那他早该在医院里好起来了
He'd have gotten better at the hospital.
这不是个套
It's not a trap.
听上去你底气不足啊
Did I hear a question markat/the end of that sentence?
- House 她.../- 我挂了
- house,look,she's--/- gotta go.
经理说可以按那个价格卖给你们
Manager says I can do that price.
杜松子酒都是粉丝送的礼物
The gin bottles are all gifts from fans.
剧中Brock Sterling喝杜松子酒/但Evan自己滴酒不沾
Brock sterling drinks it on the/show,but evan doesn't drink at all.
他现在超迷那些健康养生之道
He's on this whole health kick right now.
水果 坚果...
Fruits,nuts...
那是你从他更衣室拿的吗?
did you take those from/his dressing room?
不
No.
你不会嫁给Brock 是吧?
You're not gonna marry brock,are you?
我们等了4年 等他跟Anna修成正果
We've been waiting four years for/him to make it official with anna.
你真的是医生吗?
Are you really a doctor?
恶性胶质瘤
Glioblastoma.
还需要别的证明吗?
Need more proof?
摄影场没有有毒物质
So no toxins on the set.
他平时生活怎样?
How about his regular life?
不寻常的爱好? 声名狼藉的朋友?
Unusual hobbies? Unsavory friends?
没有 我跟他出去过
No. I've been out with him.
他跟普通人没两样
He's as vanilla as they come.
你说"出去过" 是指...
And by "out" you mean...
上个月我找他约会过
well,I asked him on a date last month.
我们出去过几回 但我们彼此不合适
We went out a few times,but/we weren't right for each other.
太小还是太大?
Too small or too large?
这跟医学相关吗?
Is that medically relevant?
我是医生 与我相关 所以与医学相关
I'm a doctor,and it's/relevant to me,so yes.
我们没到那一步
We never got that far.
我们亲热了一阵 然后他说他该回家了
We made out a while,and then/he just said he should go home.
他是个真正的绅士
He's a real gentleman.
那就有趣了
Now that'd be interesting.
他阳痿
He's impotent.
吃葵花籽节食导致的维生素B6中毒
Steady diet of sunflower/seeds causes a b6 toxicity,
会导致自主神经失调/导致小弟弟不举
which causes an autonomic dysregulation,which/causes a wood-free existence.
一晚提不起劲 加上包葵花籽/他就患上了自主神经失调?
One bad night and a couple of sunflower/seeds,and he's got autonomic dysregulation?
可不止那一晚
It's more than just one.
他都不记得上回打炮是什么时候了
He can't even remember the/last time he was able to sale.
很酷吧?
It's cool,huh?
维生素B6在毒素检查中查不出来
B6 wouldn't show upon a tox screen.
在他家也没查出什么东西
And we didn't find anything at the house.
我们要做的就是把维生素B6/从他血液里过滤掉
So all we have to do is/filter the b6 out of his blood.
给他准备血浆交换术
Prep him for plasmapheresis.
他没打炮不意味着他不能
Just because he didn't/salute doesn't mean he can't.
能找出这声音从哪儿来的吗?
And can you find out where/that voice keeps coming from?
让它从我脑子里赶出去
And tell it to get out of my head.
阳痿有可能是心理原因
The impotence could be psychological.
他情绪低落 厌恶他的工作
He's depressed. Hates his job.
血浆交换术有风险
Plasmapheresis has risks.
我们该让他晚上睡在睡眠实验室/看看他有没有反射性勃起
We should have him spend the night in the/sleep lab,see if he gets a reflex erection.
只有懦夫和祭台助手才需要证实
Confirmation is for wimps and altar boys.
不用等着看反射勃起
You don't need to wait for a reflex
如果他在正常情况下不能荷枪实弹/那他就是无能
If he can't get engorged the way/god intended,he can't get engorged.
我不会在他面前袒露乳房
I'm not showing him my boobs.
在你胸部刺激下没反应 可说明不了问题
Lack of response to your/chest tells us nothing.
13号 你给他看...
Thirteen,show him...
我去哪找一对够格的乳房呢?
Where can I find a decent/set of knockers around here?
你的A片在第二个抽屉里
Your porn's in the second drawer.
都准备好了
all set.
听觉监控器 血压监控器/还有一个放在他小弟弟上
Hear monitor,blood pressure/monitor,and the one on his junk.
这真是一种羞辱
This is humiliating.
我们把百叶窗关上 给你一些私人空间
We're gonna close the/blinds to give you some privacy.
仪器会监视你的生理反应
The instruments will let/us monitor your response.
真不明白这个人 饰演这么棒的角色
I don't get this guy. He/has the coolest gig ever,
他却感到很痛苦
but he's miserable about it.
或许他觉得放弃未必好
He probably figures/quitting won't do him any good.
觉得自己到哪里都不会开心
Figures he'd be unhappy anywhere.
环境影响了--
Our circumstances/affect whether--
这份工作让你感到很快乐 对吗?
you're pretty happy in this job,right?
当然
Sure.
你有没有过一份让你痛苦的工作?
Have you ever had a/job where you were miserable?
曾经在商场里销售男士香水
I once sold men's fragrances in/a department store.
那你痛苦吗?
And were you miserable?
薪水很低
The pay was awful.
痛苦的工作 但你不痛苦
It was a miserable job,but/you weren't miserable.
那么你呢?
So what about you?
你快乐吗?
You happy?
不怎么快乐
Not particularly.
心率加快
Heart rate and bp are climbing.
测量肿大监测器上也有反应
Got some activity on the/tumescence monitor too.
他的勃起功能没有问题
There's nothing wrong with his naughty.
并非维生素B6中毒
It's not b6 toxicity.
他这么快就结束了?
Did he just finish?
嗯...当你很久没有...你知道...
Sometimes,uh,when you/haven't,you know,for awhile,you...
他的心率急速上升
His heart rate's through the roof.
220 还在持续攀升
220 and climbing.
就快心脏病发作
He's headed for cardiac arrest.
我们电击了他的心脏 维持窦性心律
We shocked his heart/back into sinus rhythm.
至少目前看来 情况稳定
He's stable,at least for now.
可能是某种非典型性败血反应
Could be some sort of/atypical septic reaction.
但并没有发热现象
Not without a fever.
这就是我说非典型的原因
Thus the word atypical.
这样的话 我还说是非典型囊肿呢
In that case,it could/be an atypical bunion.
他吸过烟/可能是由微细胞肺癌导致的副肿瘤综合症
he used to smoke. Could be paraneoplastic/syndrome caused by small cell lung cancer.
20年前就戒了 而且他的钙水平也正常
Quit 20 years ago,and his/calcium levels are normal.
可能是甲亢
Could be graves disease.
甲状腺机能亢进可以导致系统问题
Extreme hyperthyroidism/leads to systemic problems,
包括麻痹 失明 心脏骤停
including numbness,vision/loss,and cardiac arrest.
你想在这里
You want to be here.
我不得不在这里
I have to be here.
只要你说想来 我立刻解雇13号
Just say the word,I'll fire thirteen.
继续签你的字吧
just sign the forms.
真聪明
Smart move.
我刚才是故意逗你
I was bluffing.
她是对的
She's right.
我们要在甲状腺榨干他之前 先发制敌
We should fry the/thyroid before it fries him.
我知道这样更刺激
Um,I know it's more exciting this way,
但在毁掉他身上重要的腺体前
but shouldn't we confirm you're right
我们难道不先确诊一下吗?
before destroying one of the/most important glands in his body?
如果那个腺体已在心脏上开了一个大洞/就不用
If that gland has drawn a/bull's-eye on his heart,then no.
放射摧毁甲状腺/会有让他血管损坏和癌变的危险
Nuking his thyroid puts him at risk for/vascular lesions and all kinds of cancer.
规定程序是我们应该做摄碘率测试
Protocol says we should/do an iodine uptake test.
我们?
we?
有人想在甲状腺让Brock岌岌可危之时/做这个没用的测试吗?
Anyone else want to run a useless test,while/brock's thyroid plots its next lethal move?
征求意见是开玩笑
It was rhetorical.
你之前还很确定是维B6中毒
You were sure about b-6 toxicity too.
House是对的
House is right.
真的?
Seriously?
我知道我是对的 你也这么觉得?
I mean,I am,but you think so?
如果甲状腺分泌持续增高 他会死
If he goes into full-on/thyroidstorm,he'll die.
得放射摧毁他的甲状腺
We gotta nuke his thyroid.
挂掉电话
Hang up the phone.
为什么? 如果我们要毁掉他的甲状腺...
Why? If we're gonna nuke his thyroid-
在没有确诊是甲亢之前/我们不会毁掉他的甲状腺
we're not nuking the guy's thyroid/without proof that's it's graves.
做摄碘率测试
Do the iodine uptake test.
如果House发现...
If house/finds out--
当House发现的时候
when house finds out.
我们已经有了测试结果
We'll have the test results.
要么按他说的做 要么不
And we'll either do his/procedure or we won't.
你在这里干嘛?
What are you doing here?
吃点零食
Just grabbing a snack.
你在停尸房里存放食物?
You keep food in the morgue?
我要是放在休息室 都被别人吃了
If I keep it in the/lounge,everyone else eats it.
那是因为本来就是别人的食物
That's 'causeit's everyone else's food.
哦 我还以为是别人的盒子
Oh,I thought it was/just everyone else's bags.
评估委员会会对此强烈不满
The accreditation board will/light us on fire for this.
他们不会发现
They're not gonna find out.
除非Conway计划检查停尸房/在两分钟后
Unless,of course,conway planned on/inspecting the morgue in,say,two minutes.
你是为这个来的吗?
Is that why you're here?
你会让我因为一个三明治被开除吗?
You're gonna get me/fired over a sandwich?
不会 电视机还差不多
No,over a tv.
你不会被开除 因为你会妥协
And you're not gonna get/fired because you're gonna fold.
不 我不会
No,I won't.
你会妥协的 我们需要一个安全代码/暗示你无条件投降
But you're gonna push it,so we need a safe/word to signal your unconditional surrender.
你叫我"小甜酱"
Call me sweet sauce.
House医生
Dr. House.
第一次见吧
I don't think we've met.
我是Jamie conway医生
Dr. Jamie conway.
久闻大名
I've heard your name.
大多数人都听过
Most people have.
它同样是个名词 (房子)
It's also a noun.
我有时下来放松一下 找点...
I sometimes come down here to/relax,unwind,maybe grab a--
小甜酱
sweet sauce.
这是个昵称
It's a nickname.
讽刺的昵称
An ironic nickname.
哇 都快两点了
Wow,it is almost 2:00.
你是不是应该?
Aren't you/supposed to be--?
是啊 那些失明的孩子自己无法阅读
Oh,yeah. Yeah,'cause those sick blind/kids aren't gonna read to themselves.
再见
See ya.
建议你跳过C-26柜子
I recommend skipping c-26.
一具浮尸
Floater.
至少在河里泡了一个礼拜
Been in the river at least a week.
谢谢提醒
Thanks for the warning.
随时为您效劳
Any time.
这不是休息室的电视吗?
Doesn't the doctors'/lounge have that same tv?
不 现在那里的是台12寸的小电视/和本来放在这里的一模一样
Nope,they've got a 12-inch exactly/like the one that used to be in here.
文件整理完了
Files are done.
如果我的腿脚灵便话 我会立刻劲舞一曲
I'll be doing a dance of joy just/as soon as my leg is healed.
能把那面朝下一点吗?
Can you tilt that down?
我知道你厌烦文案工作 但整理病例是很重要的
I know the paperwork annoys you,but/patient records are important.
你不能把它们扔在一边
You can't just let them sit there.
我必须这样
I had to.
以科学的名义
In the name of science.
我让垃圾堆积起来 等待最为自虐的组员
I let the crap pile up,and/then I see which team member
在忍无可忍后 清理这些垃圾
is the most self-flagellating,breaks/down,clears up the mess.
令人惊讶的是 居然是你
Surprise was,it turned out to be you.
又是你
Again.
你并不是我手下那些竞争的组员
You weren't even/registered as a competitor.
你想我了
You miss me.
是你想我了
你雇用13号就是为了代替--
You hired/thirteen to replace--
是啊 所有美女都是可以取代的
yeah,all pretty girls are fungible.
你在逃避
You're avoiding.
我想念这份工作
I miss the job.
我想念跑来跑去做私人侦探
I miss running around playing/private investigator.
我想念...那些迷题
I miss...the puzzles.
说真的 我会解雇13号
Seriously,I'll fire thirteen.
或者Kutner 如果你觉得13号很性感的话
Or kutner,if you think thirteen is hot.
但我不想念你
I don't miss you.
碘味道很奇怪
that iodine left a /really weird aftertaste.
那是追踪剂在作怪
That's the tracer in it.
过几分钟就能看见图像了
We'll have the images in/a couple of minutes.
你肯定有不少女性崇拜者
You must do okay with women,huh?
我已经问过他了
I already asked him that.
答案是?
And?
没外人想象的那么精彩
It's not all it's cracked up to be.
感觉很空虚
He feels unfulfilled.
我很怀疑
I doubt it.
我在撒谎?
I'm lying?
我曾经是一个整形医生
I used to be a plastic surgeon.
我一般都说自己的工作浅薄 没有意义
I talk about my work as/shallow and meaningless.
但其实 我爱死了隆胸 腹部除皱
Truth is,I loved every/boob job,every tummy tuck.
意义没有那么重要
Meaning doesn't mean that much.
但你不再是整形医生了
But you're not a plastic surgeon anymore.
说来话长
It's complicated.
你现在比以前更快乐吗?
Are you happier?
这很复杂
It's complicated.
他的甲状腺看起来很正常
His thyroid looks normal.
是好消息 对吗?
So that's good news,right?
你觉得看起来是不是太亮了?
Everything look too bright to you?
显示器的问题
It could be the monitor.
不是显示器
It's not the monitor.
是碘
It's the iodine.
到处都是
It's everywhere.
他的身体一点都没有吸收
His body's not filtering it.
肾脏在衰竭
His kidneys are failing.
我让你毁了他的甲状腺
I told you to nuke his thyroid.
幸亏没有这么做
It's a good thing we didn't.
肾衰竭表明并非甲亢
Kidney failure means it wasn't graves.
那么你的测试打败了我/也毁了病人的肾
So your test screwed me and/our patient's kidneys.
确切的说你让他碘中毒了
Practically poisoned him with iodine.
如果它的肾脏健康就不会碘中毒
Which he could have handled easily/if his kidneys were healthy.
我们做的只是揭示了一个新症状
All we did was reveal a new symptom.
通常 这会是你想要的
Usually,you're all for that.
肯定是你腐臭的背叛气息倒了我的胃口
Must be the rancid tinge of/betrayal that's put me off.
你判断错了
You were wrong.
那就正面告诉我啊
So tell me to my face.
你之前从不犹豫
You never hesitated before.
委员会让你变成一个懦夫了
The board's turned you into a coward.
我那样做是因为那是正确的事情
I did it because it/was the right thing to do.
你那样做是为了通过审查
You did it to pass an inspection.
这重要吗?
Does it matter?
肾衰竭加上其他症状 表明这是自身免疫系统问题
Kidney failure on top of the other/symptoms points to an autoimmune condition,
也就是接下来任何一个器官都可能出问题
which means that any of his/other organs could be next.
我们已经开始给他做透析
We've already started dialysis.
我们现在需要测抗核抗体/来确诊是自身免疫的问题
We need to run anas for autoimmune.
你说的对
You're right.
你和其他成员 去测量天花板吧
You and the team,go/measure the ceilings.
抱歉?
Excuse me?
评估委员会的准则有写到/物品离天花板的距离要大于18英寸
Accreditation board guidelines state that no/object can be less than 18 inches from the ceiling.
确保我们的都符合标准
Make sure we're in compliance.
我们办公室里没有不符合要求的...
There's nothing in our/office that would be less--
我说的不是我们 是整个医院
I don't mean us. I/mean the whole hospital.
我们试试新床怎么样
Let's see how this baby handles.
怎么了?
What?
你买了硬床垫
You bought the firm mattress.
我以为这是你喜欢的
I thought that's the one you wanted.
是
It was.
你为什么这么做?
Why would you do that?
因为...
Because—
是脑筋急转弯吗?
This is a trick question?
我想让你自己拿主意
I left it up to you.
你应该买你自己喜欢的
You were supposed to/get the one you wanted.
我是因为爱你 才买了你想要的
I got the one you/wanted because I love you.
不是
No.
你这么做是因为你一贯如此
You did it because that's what you do.
就像对所有的前妻一样/你尽力满足她们的需求 因为那样更省事
With all your ex-wives,you did whatever/they wanted because it was easier,
可最后都以你对她们厌恶告终
and you ended up resenting them.
你别想那么对我
Don't you dare do that to to me.
什么 照顾你吗?
What,take care of you?
你还不了解我吗?
Have you met me?
我能照顾自己
I can take care of me.
我要你照顾好自己
I need you to take care of you.
我得做事了
I have work to do.
你在第8页
You made it to page eight.
"肥皂剧中的医生神秘造访医院"
"Mysterious hospital visit for soap doc."
喔 我该给我妈妈寄一份
Wow,I'll be sure to send my mom a copy.
他们告诉我 我患的是自身免疫疾病
They told me I have/an autoimmune disease.
像狼疮或肉状瘤
Like lupus or sarcoidosis.
我们也想知道是不是
That's what we're here to find out.
你是不是真的如大家想的那么厉害?
You really as good as/everyone seems to think you are?
你是不是真像大家想的那么可怜呢?
Are you really as miserable as/everyone seems to think you are?
我只想做些有意义的事
I just want to do something that matters.
没有有意义的事
Nothing matters.
我们不过是凡夫俗子
We're all just cockroaches.
羚羊死在河边
Wildebeests dying on the river bank.
没什么事情会有永恒的意义
Nothing we do has any lasting meaning.
你认为我很可悲
And you think I'm miserable.
如果你在飞机上不开心的话/跳下来就是
If you're unhappy on/the plane,jump out of it.
我也想 可我办不到
I want to,but...I can't.
嗯 这就是暗喻的问题所在
Hmm,that's the problem with metaphors.
需要解释一下
They need interpretation.
从飞机上往下跳是件很愚蠢的事
Jumping out of the plane is stupid.
要是我不在飞机上呢?
Well,what if I'm not in a plane?
而是在一个我不想待的地方呢?
What if I'm just in a/place I don't want to be?
这又是暗喻的另一个问题了
That's the other problem with metaphors.
你在一辆冰淇淋车上/ 被糖果 鲜花 美女簇拥 怎么样?
Yes,what if you're actually in an ice cream truck/and outside are candy and flowers and virgins?
你是在飞机上
You're on a plane.
我们都在飞机上
We're all on planes.
生活很危险也很复杂
Life is dangerous and complicated.
路也很长
And it's a long way down.
那么你害怕改变咯?
So you're afraid of change?
不 是你怕
No,you're afraid to change.
你幻想自己能逃避 却不愿尝试
You'd rather imagine that you can/escape instead of actually try.
因为你一旦失败 就会一无所有
'Cause if you fail,then/you've got nothing.
所以你不愿真正去尝试/这样你至少还有期望
So you'll give up the chance of something/real so that you can hold on to hope.
问题是 期望是留给孬种的
The thing is,hope is for sissies.
等我出去之后 我什么都不会怕了
When I get outta here,I'm/not gonna be afraid anymore.
有多少人能有再来一次的机会?
I mean,how many guys get a second chance?
多得是
Too many.
一半我救的人都不配有这个机会
Half the people I save don't/deserve a second chance.
既然我有这个机会/我就要洗心革面
Now that I've got mine,I'm/gonna set things right.
我要做你的好爸爸
I'm gonna start by being a/better father to you.
做你妹妹的好爸爸
And to your sister.
还有你另一个妹妹的
And to your other sister.
你知道自己在背上一季的台词吧
You realize you're reciting/lines from last season.
我会履行我所有的承诺
We're gonna do all the things I promised.
只要能让我从这床上起来
Just help me get out of this bed.
快拿冷却毯过来
Cooling blankets in here.
他的脑袋快要烧爆了
This guy's brain is about to boil.
知道自己在哪吗?
Do you know where you are?
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
Brock Sterling医生
Dr. Brock sterling.
发烧说明不是自体免疫疾病
fever rules out auto-immune.
他得的是败血症
He's septic.
严重感染了
He's got a massive infection.
我们给他注射了广谱抗生素/可是他仍不仅胡言乱语 还陷入昏迷
we've got him on broad spectrum antibiotics,/but he slipped from delirium into a coma.
好消息是Brock上次昏迷的时候/做了两个孩子的爸
Good news is last time brock was/in a coma he fathered two children.
我们得找出感染病因/快点给他对症下药
We need to identify the infection and/get him on more targeted meds fast.
会不会是肺炎球菌?
What about pneumococcus?
会导致心脏衰竭以及败血症
Causes heart problems and sepsis.
可那不会影响到足部跟眼部的神经
But not the neuropathies in/his foot and eyes.
破伤风呢?
What about tetanus?
他去年打过破伤风疫苗
he got a tetanus booster last year.
莱姆关节炎?
Lyme disease?
那他会全身酸痛
He would've been sore all over.
至少有1000种感染病因能导致这种症状
There's 1,000 infections/that could've caused this.
我们可以一项项试验/可他在培养出结果前就会死翘翘了
We can start testing,but he'll/be dead  before the cultures grow.
除非是真菌感染
Unless it's a fungus.
我们在显微镜下就能看见
We could see that under a microscope.
做一下真菌 寄生虫测试/所有渺小而顽强的生物
Test for fungi,parasites,all/creatures great and small.
你去哪儿?
Where you going?
去躺一下
To lie down.
我要思考一下
I need to think.
可能是鼠咬热
Could be rat bite fever...
可他的淋巴又没有肿
but his glands aren't swollen.
你准备买哪张?
Which one are you gonna get?
她让我想买哪张买哪张
she told me to get the one I want.
那就买呗
So get it.
李斯特杆菌可以解释败血/心脏衰竭也能说得通
Listeria explains the sepsis,possibly/also the heart problem.
可无法解释麻痹
But not the numbness.
如果李斯特杆菌引起脑脊髓炎/就能引起麻痹...
If the listeria caused encephalomyelitis,which/then caused the numbness...
我想要张水床
I want a waterbed.
我一直都想要一张
I've always wanted one.
我知道这很滑稽 只是...
I know it's ridiculous. It's just--
一想到被水簇拥着入睡/就觉得很炫
there's something nice about the thought/of being rocked to sleep in water.
你不打算嘲笑我?
No mocking?
不准备做一番弗洛伊德式的评析/例如水床暗示着我想钻入女人阴道?
No freudian analysis of how the waterbed is/really a great big vagina I want to crawl into?
我忽视你是因为 你让我很伤心
I'm ignoring you because you make me sad.
他用了氨苄/如果是李斯特杆菌的话 他应该有所好转
He's on ampicillin,which means if it was/listeria,he'd have shown some improvement.
不 你得换全套
No,it's a whole thing.
你得要专门的床单和保险...
You need special/sheets and insurance--
那又怎样?
who cares?
你一直都想要
You wanted one your whole life.
你是个成年人了
You're a grown-up.
你买得起 商店也有卖的
You can afford it. Stores sell them.
大多数成年人不像你那样 House/随便起个怪点子 都非得满足
Most adults don't go through life like/you do,house,indulging our every whim.
活该你快活不起来
You don't deserve to be happy.
我很快活啊
And yet I am.
你呢?
You?
Amber会觉得这很可笑的
Amber'll think it's stupid.
是很可笑
It is stupid.
去实现你的梦想吧 Wilson
Live the dream,wilson.
这不是传染病
it's not an infection.
是过敏
It's an allergy.
这就是为什么抗生素不起作用的原因
That's why it's not/responding to antibiotics.
这可不是拍电视 House
This isn't a soap opera,house.
你不能一给病人下药/就指望他会立马苏醒
People don't just wake up from/comas the second you give 'em drugs.
特别是下错药的时候
Especially if we give/him the wrong drugs.
检验结果如何?
What do the sts say?
真菌和寄生虫的结果呈阴性/不过也不能说明...
It was negive for fungus and/parasites,but that doesn't mean—
我们排除的感染越多/就越说明这不是感染
the more infections we rule out,the more/likely it is that it's not an infection.
他没有过敏或哮喘病史
He has no history of allergies or asthma.
最重要的是/他没有一个症状与过敏反应相似
Most importantly,none of his symptoms/remotely resemble an allergic reaction.
过敏原会导致过敏性血管炎
Allergens could trigger an/allergic vasculitis.
那就可以解释所有症状了
That would explain the symptoms.
百万分之一的几率
One in a million times.
败血性感染能解释他的症状
Septic infection always/explains his symptoms.
没有一种感染能抵御所有抗生素
But an infection is never/resistant to every antibiotic.
不 是感染少有抗药性
No,infection is rarely resistant.
而抗生素从来对过敏症没作用
And allergy never/responds to antibiotics.
"从不"打败"很少"
Never beats rarely.
证明完毕 我赢了
Qed,I win.
他的更衣室里有菊花
There were chrysanthemums in/his dressing room.
上帝 你干嘛不说他暴露于地球生物
My god,why didn't you say/he'd been exposed to plant life.
菊花里面含有除虫菊酯
Chrysanthemums contain pyrethrin.
一种神经毒素 也是种过敏原
It's a neurotoxin and a known allergen.
他得的是感染
He has an infection.
给他注射类固醇的话 会害死他的
If we give him steroids,we'll kill him.
他得的是过敏症
He has an allergy.
不给他类固醇 才是让他死
If we don't give him/steroids,we'll kill him.
可没死得这么快
Not as fast.
会很快的
Fast enough.
你没时间做其他的检测了/我们不能坐以待毙
You don't have time for the rest of/the tests. We have to do something.
我们现在做的没起作用
And what we're doing/right now isn't working.
100毫克甲强龙
100 milligrams methylprednisolone.
哪些病人?
Patients' names?
只有一个病人
It's one patient.
你要给一个病人100毫克的剂量?
You want to give one/patient 100 milligrams?
那足够启动一辆车的了
That'll jump start a car.
正好 因为我的病人刚好/是辆陷入昏迷的69年产福特
Perfect,'cause my/patient's a '69 ford coma.
超过50毫克需要Cuddy医生的签名
Anything over 50 milligrams,I/need a sign-off from Dr. Cuddy.
这是规矩
It's protocol.
视察员也在这儿呢
And the inspector's here.
我99%确定她一定会同意的
I am 99% certain that she'll consent.
不过鉴于那1%的可能性/要不我就自己...
But for the sake of the/1% why don't I just--
你不能进来
you're not allowed back here.
你可以让视察员记我一笔
Well,tell the inspector he/can put it on my tab.
我不是说现在
I didn't mean now.
100毫克的甲强龙过量了
100 milligrams of/methylprednisolone is an overdose.
我们搞错了 不是感染
We were wrong about the infection.
他这是严重过敏反应
He's suffering from a/severe allergic reaction.
小组没有进行过敏测试
The team hasn't finished/the test for allergy.
他的症状不是...
His symptoms don't--
在极少情况下...
in rare cases--
相信我 到最后 我是对的
trust me,at the end of this/conversation,I'm right.
那就证明给我看
Then confirm it.
给他验血
Get a blood test.
这么严重深度的昏迷
What is it about this/severe and deepening coma
你居然还觉得有时间按规章办?
that makes you think we/got time for protocol?
管理规章已经防止你的病人/甲状腺受损 血液被抽干
Protocol has saved your patient from having/his thyroid destroyed and his blood drained.
如果你觉得我错了 就直说
If you think I'm/wrong,tell me I'm wrong.
别给我提规章
Don't talk about protocol.
我的工作岌岌可危
My job's on the line.
你也是
Your job is on the line.
好吧 你这么办 等我三分钟/然后你就叫保安
Okay,here's what you do: You wait/three minutes,then you call security.
他们来拷我的时候/我的事也做完了
By the time they get here and/lock me up,I'll be done.
他可以接着活下去
He gets to live.
也能保住你的位子
Your ass gets to be covered.
如果他死了 告诉我...
If he dies,let me know...
好让我收拾东西滚蛋
so I can pack my things.
*昨夜感觉真好*
*Last night it was so good*
*我想哭*
I felt like crying*
*昨夜虽然你冷冷淡淡*
*last night though you looked so cold*
*可我想笑*
*I felt like smiling*
*我想笑着死去*
*smiling when I'm dying*
*昨夜真的感觉不错*
*last night looked so good*
*我想哭*
*I felt like crying*
*昨夜你看起来苍老*
*last night though you looked so old*
*可我想笑*
*I felt like smiling*
*想笑着死去*
*smiling while I'm dying*
*你留下我冷冷冰冰*/歌名: Needles In My Eyes/演唱: the Beta Band
*you left me cold*
*你留下我冷冷冰冰*
结果呈阴性
tests are negative.
病人对所有花类敏感症测试呈阴性
Patient's negative for/all floral allergies.
我要重新给他用抗生素
I'm gonna restart the antibiotics.
如果他还活着的话
If he's still alive.
静脉注射2克氨苄
Ampicillin,two grams,iv.
为什么?
Why?
类固醇起作用了
The steroids worked.
House是对的
House was right.
但检测结果阴性
The test was negative.
他还是说对了
He was still right.
是过敏症
It was an allergy.
对什么过敏?
To what?
谢谢
Thank you.
我错了
I was wrong.
你该阻止我
You should've stopped me.
我听说了House的病人
Heard about house's patient.
太大胆了
Bold move.
你支持他
And you backed him.
他是对的
He was right.
他离正确十万八千里
He wasn't even in the/same neighborhood as right.
病人活下来了
The patient's alive.
在95%的情况下 对95%的人
Okay,the rules exist because 95%/of the time for 95% of the people,
按规矩办事没错
they're the right thing to do.
那另外5%呢?
And the other 5%?
也得照规矩做
Have to live by the same rules.
不然每个人都有例外可作借口
Because everybody/thinks they're in that 5%.
你在外面干嘛?
What are you doing out here?
我睡不着
I can't sleep.
我讨厌水床
I hate the waterbed.
我倒有点喜欢
I actually kind of like it.
不 难受死了
No,it's awful.
明天就去把它退了
We're returning it tomorrow.
好吧
Okay.
你想通了真好
I'm glad you got it though.
我也觉得
Me too.
希望他们肯退货
I hope they'll take it back.
他们会的
They will.
你答应过我不再酗酒
You promised me you'd stop drinking.
我就是喝醉了 Anna
Of course I'm drunk,anna.
他们都说你昏迷了 再也醒不过来
They told me you'd never/wake up from that coma.
你怎么能和我妹妹订婚?
But how could you get/engaged to my sister?
我们相爱了
we fell in love.
你想我怎么做 Anna?
What do you want from me,anna?
我是个男人
I'm just a man.
我也只是个女人
and I'm just a woman.
我很激动
And as thrilled as I am/about the lady slipper
Lady Slipper成了Lawrence港最好的夜店
being the best night club/port lawrence has ever seen—
喂?
Hello?
别挂
don't hang up.
结论怎么样?
What was the verdict?
罚款200,000元
$200,000 fine.
你真该被解雇
You should've been fired.
晚安House
Good night,house.
他的酒杯里有气泡
There are bubbles in his glass.
就不能等到天--
Can't this wait until--
病人是对奎宁过敏
my patient is allergic to quinine.
你从气泡想到的?
And you got this from bubbles?
症状在两个月前出现
symptoms started two months ago.
恰恰是Brock开始喝杜松子酒的时候/学英国人饮杜松子酒抵御疟疾
It's also when brock started downing gin/and tonics like a brit staving off malaria.
杜松子酒是假的 奎宁水却是真的
The gin was fake,the tonic was real.
奎宁水含很多奎宁
And tonic water is loaded with quinine.
真不错
Nice job.
你真该被解雇了
You should've been fired.
我收回电视机
I'm taking back the tv.
我救了他的命
I saved his life.
这不是我们订立的条件
That wasn't the deal.
合同写明了不能出尔反尔
The contract clearly/stated no takesy backsies.
晚安 House
Good night,house.
你穿着什么?
What are you wearing?
晚安 House
Good night,house.
晚安 Cuddy
Good night,cuddy.